conspiracyoftherich.com 2010-09-19

# Privacy policy | Conspiracy of the Rich: The 8 New Rules of Money

| 

The following terms and conditions govern the online Privacy Policy for the web site for [www.ConspiracyoftheRich.com](http://www.conspiracyoftherich.com/) (the “Site” or “Web Site”), a Site made available by **The Rich Dad Company** (“Rich Dad” or “we” or “us”). 

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, at any time without notice to you, by posting such changes on the Site.

**BY USING THE SITE, YOU ACCEPT AND AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF USE AS APPLIED TO YOUR USE OF THE SITE, INCLUDING FOR THE THIRD PARTY BENEFIT OF ROBERT KIYOSAKI (the “AUTHOR”).**

If you do not agree to the revised Privacy Policy, you should not access or otherwise use the Site.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as, accessing media files, Rich Dad may ask you to register and provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online registration form. It is optional for you to provide your information and engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, Rich Dad may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address and telephone number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

Any and all personal information collected through the Site, including through registration or otherwise, shall belong to Rich Dad. Please note: If you are located outside of the United States, note that information that you provide to us is being sent to the United States. By using this Site and registering, you understand and consent to your data being sent to the United States. 

**Rich Dad’s Use of Personal Information**  
Personal information collected through this site may be made available to Hachette Book Group, Inc., the Work’s publisher. Hachette may use such information in accordance with its own online Privacy Policy. <http://www.hachettebookgroup.com/privacy-policy.aspx>

**Security**  
We will take reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of all personal information provided to this Site. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

**Other Eyeballs**  
Please note that any information you post to a public discussion forum or chat room, such as Discussion Forums, is available to all persons accessing that part of the Site. We have no way of preventing individuals or companies from contacting you if they've seen your information publicly posted. For this reason, we recommend that you do not submit your full name, home address, phone number, or other information that would enable other users to locate you, or submit any information you regard as sensitive, such as financial information, on these areas of our Web site. We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is or may be causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Web site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

**Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are delicious. Some sections of our site utilize cookies as a convenience for our visitors. As an example - whenever a visitor fills out an online form, we set a cookie, and if accepted, it will prevent the visitor from having to reenter their information for any other online form on the site. So if you provide your info on our Contact form, you will not be required to fill out the Online Video access form. However, you will be required to enter your information on our Order System as we need the most current information you can provide for order fulfillment. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. While the Rich Dad Company uses cookies to track your visit to [ConspiracyoftheRich.com](http://www.conspiracyoftherich.com/), and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided the Rich Dad Company with personal information.

**Consistency**  
Please note that if you provide the Rich Dad Company with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that we may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that we may not), the Rich Dad Company cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored. Outside Sites, please note that the Rich Dad Company is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Rich Dad Company websites to which [ConspiracyoftheRich.com](http://www.conspiracyoftherich.com/) or any other Rich Dad Company website may link.

If you have further questions, e-mail: [privacy@conspiracyoftherich.com](mailto:privacy@conspiracyoftherich.com)

The Rich Dad Company  
4330 N Civic Center, Plz # 101  
Scottsdale, AZ‎ 85251

Dated: January 19, 2009

|
